Megan Brosovich

Network Operations Specialist

Levittown, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Megan-Brosovich/db0ab2b627e02222

Pharmacy technician who is career oriented and dedicated with 6 years experience in retail and mail order pharmacies. Expertise includes pharmacy knowledge, customer service/relations, inventory management and pharmacy/Microsoft software. Consistently collaborated with managers and team members to meet goals and produce quality results.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Network Operations Specialist

PHILIDOR RX SERVICES LLC - Hatboro, PA - December 2014 to March 2016

- * Traveled to network pharmacy sites; participated in the initial build-out and trained location staff on company policies and procedures.
- * Developed SOP's for network sites by collaborating with team members and leadership.
- * Communicated with outside vendors in order to facilitate outsourced projects.
- * Engaged in the initial inventory and stock, keeping accurate records and counts.
- * Cross trained to be able to increase line production by 25% on average.

Senior Pharmacy Technician

- * Prepared and distributed patient medications under the direct supervision of a licensed pharmacist.
- * Read and verified prescriptions for accuracy and completeness in a mail order environment; shipping 10,000+ prescriptions a day.
- * Systematized, counted and filled pharmacy orders, while maintaining a growing queue.
- * Printed and labeled prescriptions; prepared orders for shipment.
- * Upheld compliance with state and or federal laws, rules and regulations.
- * Maintained clean, organized and professional work station, adhering to company standards.
- * Researched and corrected patient demographic information, adjudication errors and shipping errors.
- * Ordered medications through wholesaler; ensured accurate inventory throughout the pharmacy.
- * Monitored all priority prescriptions to ensure punctual delivery of patient medication.

Pharmacy Technician

PARKWOOD STREET ROAD PHARMACY - Bensalem, PA - March 2010 to December 2014

- * Gathering medications off pharmacy shelves, counting and dispensing prescriptions to patients.
- * Ordering medications, medical equipment and pharmacy items from wholesaler; maintaining inventory throughout the pharmacy.
- * Coordinated with store manager about inventory supplies.
- * Adjudicated prescriptions and printed prescription labels on HBS computer system; labeled prescription vials.
- * Assisted customers with durable medical equipment; sizing of braces to ensure proper comfort and functionality.
- * Answered phones for refills on patient medications and any other questions the customer needed.

EDUCATION

Associates

Bucks County School of Beauty Culture Graduate

October 2006 to April 2008